{
    "id": "0c41958aad844b84a012b590d21140a0",
    "title": "Verb + Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ………………… me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ad3dc9c23f44e4288777826bcbdabbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like you to listen ………………….. this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c4e889a22063412c8ebea5914d75263a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let us talk ………………… your new projects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "13c47b84c41b47318b5ea67308da11fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ran ………………… James at Victoria Station yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6758cfd6353b447a9a02324599f2a073"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you been married ………………… her?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce59644aa26c4270af2b8925e3c41e86"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am thinking ………………….. studying engineering.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7be7d853cc742299e03962fc223ec90"
        },
        {
            "question": "A week after the accident he died ………………… his injuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ca5da5f6fa74861bf919a260b3532d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I half believe …………………. life after death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eca0ae33d7a74b16b84298bc2eee058d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must apologize ............................... disturbing you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1cbbcf25be54763a34e7464b08f4269"
        },
        {
            "question": "He left the firm because he didn’t agree ................................... their sales policy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "51a7c474ddd444719ff577e7ad50df23"
        }
    ]
}